Dear Black people, Juneteenth is our day.
You don't have to feel any kind of way about white people not being included in Juneteenth,
because they are included in Juneteenth as the descendants of enslavers.
But Juneteenth should be about unity.
Why?
This country is not about unity.
Juneteenth is an American holiday.
If you're not going to teach true history in American schools,
then don't come trying to take Black holidays and call them American holidays.
The point is, is that Black folks can be all right celebrating a day for Black folks
without feeling like we have to include other folks.
I don't see Christians spinning dreidels for Hanukkah ads.
Ba-dum-ba!